PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name

Shaba, Japhet Oluwaseun

Address

FUTA South Gate, Akure, Ondo State.

Cell Phone Number +2348063050592

Email

japhetsoj53@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hardworking individual with high expertise in HTML, BOOTSTRAP, JavaScript, Jquery, and PHP as well as ability to interact effectively in a team setting, and possessing a strong willingness to learn more about utilizing technical, management skills, and the emerging trends in the IT sector seeks to apply for the position of a backend Web Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE/WORK PLACEMENT

MARCH, 2021 - SEPTEMBER, 2021

Liverpetal System, Akure, Ondo State – Full Stack Web Developer (Intern)

Managing and improving existing company's projects alongside other interns under the supervision of other developers and as well, putting other interns through in times of difficulties and challenges faced in the course of learning and finishing given tasks.

SEPTEMBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

AXIOS, Lagos, Nigeria —Backend Developer

Working alongside front-end and backend developers and designers to deliver first hand and modern dynamic web applications.

NOVEMBER 2021 -Till Date

Hespat Technology, Akure, Ondo State - Backend Web Developer

- Responsible for creating and testing applications for websites. Collaborating alongside other developers, and graphic designers.
- * Responsible for creation, consumption and implementation of APIs
- Monitored website traffic and troubleshoot website problems.

EDUCATION

2014

St. Dominic's Secondary School, Akure, Ondo State — (Senior School Certificate)

2016 - Till Date

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY, AKURE (FUTA) — Currently in my final year.

PERSONAL APTITUDE

- Effective management of a unique balanced state both physically and emotionally.
- analyzing wants and needs and also ready to adapt to any changes my clients like to see implemented on the website.
- Possess a good sense of humor. Spreading positivity to other developers and every member of the team.
- Willingness to learn always.
- Well functioning critical thinking skills.
- Exercising leadership skills and also showing willingness to grow and adapt at your own pace.

SKILLS/COMPETENCES

- → Good analytical, planning, and problem solving skills.
- → Good accuracy and attention to details.
- → Excellent problem analysis
- → Vast knowledge in HTML, BOOTSTRAP, VANILLA, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, MYSQL, and PHP.

HOBBIES

- → Coding
- → Researching
- → Making goal focused (developers) friends.
- → Traveling
- → Being creative
- → Listening to music

REFERENCE

Available upon request.